macvendors.com 2001-06-16

# MegaMac.com

To protect your privacy, MegaMac.com follows the following principles for privacy and data protection. 

**WHY WE OBTAIN INFORMATION**

> We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a new account on one of our web sites to use specific features available only to registered users. 
> 
> The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to access more features. We may also periodically use your information to alert you to updated information and other new services from MegaMac.com. 
> 
> If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features MegaMac.com web sites. But you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.  
> 

**REGISTERED USER PROFILES**

> When you register for services such as an email account or for accounts on web sites such as Mac-Events.com and Mac-Classifieds.com, your information is protected by use of a password which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password which is neither common or known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password. 
> 
> If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means. 
> 
> We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the related links provided on our web sites, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. 

**NOTICE TO PARENTS**

> Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. Even more, we'd like to encourage parents to supervise their children's activities online and to participate with their children whenever possible.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED IN AD DELIVERY**

> MegaMac.com has a relationship with the Sonar Network, a business unit of DoubleClick Inc., to provide us with an ad management solution. In the course of delivering an ad to you, DoubleClick does not collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. DoubleClick does, however, collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), and whether you responded to the ad delivered. The non-personally identifiable information collected by DoubleClick is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of DoubleClick's advertisers and Web publishers who specifically request it. For additional information on the information that is collected by DoubleClick in the process of delivering an ad to you, please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm).
